crosswordtracker.com 2017-12-19

# Crossword Tracker Privacy Policy - crossword puzzle tracker

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Crossword Tracker collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Crossword Tracker’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Crossword Tracker’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Crossword Tracker may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

Crossword Tracker may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Crossword Tracker may monitor the most popular clues or answers of a time period on the site or use analytics to help identify automated abuses. Crossword Tracker may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Crossword Tracker does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Crossword Tracker uses cookies to help Crossword Tracker identify and track visitors, their usage of Crossword Tracker website, and their website access preferences. Crossword Tracker visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Crossword Tracker’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Crossword Tracker’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

#### Business Transfers

If Crossword Tracker, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Crossword Tracker goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Crossword Tracker may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Crossword Tracker and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Third party vendors, including Google and its subsideraries, may set or use cookies for targeted advertising. You may opt out of Google's interest-based advertising program by visiting their [ads prereferences manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). 

#### Analytics

Crossword Tracker makes use of Google Analytics to gather statistics and demographics about visitors. Demographic data gathered includes Age, Gender, and Interest. Visitors can opt-out or customize what demographic data is captured by using Google's [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) feature. 

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Crossword Tracker may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Crossword Tracker’s sole discretion. Crossword Tracker encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
